ooma.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Free Home Phone Service | Ooma – Ranked # 1 Internet Home Phone Service

Last Updated: November 24, 2014

Ooma Inc. (“Ooma”) is committed to your privacy. We obey all laws and regulations in the United States applicable to our use and disclosure of your information. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we will not trade, sell, or disclose to any third party any form of Personal Information (as defined below) without your consent, and we will not disclose or make available any such Personal Information to any third parties seeking to market third party products without your consent. We have set forth this Policy to explain how we collect and use information from customers who use Ooma Equipment and Services (“Customers”), as fully defined in the Terms and Conditions which appear on our web site, which are incorporated by reference herein, and from visitors to our web sites and potential customers who have communicated, made contact with, or interacted with Ooma (“Visitors”), both in connection with online and offline Services and Equipment offered by Ooma.

### Collection of Information

Ooma shall collect information, including, but not limited to, name, physical address, email address, telephone number, credit card information, and other Customer-supplied data (collectively referred to as “Personal Information”) from Customers when purchasing Equipment and Services in connection with the provision or marketing of Equipment and Services. Ooma may collect Personal Information from Visitors in connection with any visit to our web sites, any communication about our Services and Equipment, or other transactions or interactions with Ooma.

Ooma may also collect non-personally identifiable information from Customers and Visitors regarding usage of our Services or our web site (“Non-Personal Information”). Non-Personal Information may include web site pages viewed, time spent using certain services, demographic data, cookies (as described below), and other information which does not specifically identify an individual party.

“Cookies” are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. We may use cookies to customize your visit to our web sites and for other purposes to improve your online user experience and to enable us to enhance our web site, Equipment, and Services.

In addition to cookies, Ooma (and our third party advertisers) may also use clear gifs, web beacons, and third party cookies to improve the performance of our web sites, provide certain features, such as advertising, or to anonymously track usage of our web sites and track the online activity of users. In addition, we may use such devices in our HTML-based emails to track the usage of such emails in much the same manner as we track usage of our web sites.

You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer, including third party cookies, or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our web site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality.

Or, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Use of Information

Ooma will use Personal Information (1) to market our Equipment and Services to Customers and to Visitors that Ooma believes have interest in them, (2) to provide Services and Equipment requested by Customers and Visitors and (3) to enable its vendors and contractors to provide and assist Ooma in the marketing and provision of such Equipment and Services to Ooma Customers and Visitors. However, we will not share your credit card information with any third parties unless they are involved in processing payments for Equipment and Services that you have procured from Ooma. Ooma only works with partners whom we believe maintain high standards with respect to privacy and consumer rights.

Ooma may also use and disclose Personal Information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of our service or network, to investigate fraud or violations of our Customer Agreement as required by courts or administrative agencies, or in connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of Ooma’s business.

Non-Personal Information may be shared with any number of third parties by Ooma.

### Customer Specific Network Information

In the course of providing Services to you, Ooma will collect and maintain certain customer-specific network information. Customer Specific Network Information refers to the types of products and services you currently purchase, related usage, and billing information for those products and services. Your telephone number, name, and address are not Customer Specific Network Information. Likewise, customer usage and call patterns of multiple customers which is aggregated together in a summary form and other information which does not specifically identify any one individual is not considered Customer Specific Network Information. We value our relationships with our customers and are committed to respecting and protecting your Customer Specific Network Information. Accordingly, we will not sell, trade, or share your Customer Specific Network Information, including your calling records outside of Ooma or with anyone not authorized to offer our Equipment and/or Services, or to perform functions on our behalf except as authorized by you or required by law. Generally, we can use your Customer Specific Network Information to offer additional Services to you, and for billing and collections purposes. We can also disclose your Customer Specific Information for legal or regulatory reasons, including in response to subpoenas and court orders. We can also use Customer Specific Network Information to investigate fraud and to prevent violation of our End User Agreement and monitor potentially unlawful use of our network, Services, and abuse of other customers.

### Security

Ooma has exercised reasonable care to investing and deploy a wide variety of technology and security features to ensure the privacy of information on its network. In addition, Ooma has implemented operations guidelines to ensure Customer and Visitor privacy. Ooma will continue to revise policies and implement additional security features as new technologies becomes available. However, no system or service can offer a 100% guaranty of security, especially a service that relies upon the public Internet and public phone system. Therefore, your consent serves to acknowledge the risk that third parties may gain unauthorized access to your information and conversations when using our Equipment and Services.

### Communications

Ooma will not listen to or disclose to any third parties conversations, voice messages, or other communications that are transmitted using Ooma Equipment and Services except as required to ensure proper operation of Equipment and Services or as otherwise authorized by law.

You should be aware that any Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit through publicly accessible forums (i.e., such as chat rooms, blogs, instant messages,) may be viewed and used by anyone with access to such forums. Ooma is unable to control such uses of your Personal Information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

### Account Information

Subject to certain security requirements, Ooma will do its best to honor requests from Customers for account information, for example, name, address, company, or billing information. The Customer is responsible for ensuring that the information on file with Ooma is current and accurate. Ooma does not knowingly sell Equipment or Services to, or knowingly solicit or collect Personal Information from, anyone under the age of eighteen.

### Third Party Web Sites and Services

Our service may contain links to other web sites and services not maintained by Ooma, which are outside our control. In addition, other web sites and services may make reference or link to Ooma. We are not responsible for third party representations of our Equipment and Services. We encourage customers who surf the Internet to read the applicable privacy statements of each and every web site and service you visit. We do not endorse, screen, or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites and services.

Ooma does not assume any liability for third parties that have been provided with information as permitted by this Privacy Policy or who have collected information as permitted by this Privacy Policy (such as advertisers using third party cookies).

### Affiliates and Sponsors

Some Ooma Equipment and Services are offered to Customers and Visitors in conjunction with a third-party vendor To provide these products and services, the vendor may need to collect and maintain your Personal Information. Additionally, Ooma may share non-identifying and aggregate Customer and Visitor Personal Information with such affiliates in order to market our co-branded Equipment and Services more effectively to Customers.

### Online Advertisements

Ooma may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Customers collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with select advertisers. In some instances, we use this information to deliver tailored advertisements. Based upon the information we have collected, we may then display advertisements to specific audiences. Ooma does not share Personal Information about its Customers with these advertisers.

### Voluntary Surveys

Ooma may periodically conduct both business and individual surveys. We encourage Customers to participate in these voluntary surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of Services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your Personal Information and responses will remain confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third-party.

Ooma uses the information we receive from individuals in response to our surveys and combines (or aggregates) this information with that provided by other Customers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our Services to you, and to develop new Services and Equipment. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third-party affiliates.

### Changes to Policy

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Policy at any time by posting such changes on our web site. You should review this Policy regularly for changes, and can easily identify if changes have been made by checking the “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use Personal Information in a way that materially differs from this Policy, we will post such changes on our web site and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of such differing terms of usage. Your continued use of our Equipment and Services for a reasonable period of time following the posting of any changes to this Policy means you accept such changes.

### Customer Agreement

This Privacy Policy is subject to the Ooma Customer Agreement and any other agreements between you and Ooma. If you are a Customer, please refer to the Customer Agreement or other such agreements regarding certain rights and limitations with respect to your use of Ooma’s Equipment and Services.
